{"All_data": [{"Country": "Belgi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "4.8", "Justice system": "4.4", "Police": "5.6", "Politicians": "4.3", "Parliament": "5.0", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.9", "UN": "5.1"}, {"Country": "Belgi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "4.8", "Justice system": "4.8", "Police": "5.8", "Politicians": "4.2", "Parliament": "4.7", "Political Parties": "4.3", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "5.1"}, {"Country": "Belgi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "5.0", "Justice system": "4.9", "Police": "5.9", "Politicians": "4.4", "Parliament": "5.0", "Political Parties": "4.4", "European Parliament": "5.1", "UN": "5.3"}, {"Country": "Belgi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "5.1", "Justice system": "4.9", "Police": "6.0", "Politicians": "4.0", "Parliament": "4.6", "Political Parties": "4.0", "European Parliament": "5.1", "UN": "5.3"}, {"Country": "Belgi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "5.0", "Justice system": "4.9", "Police": "6.0", "Politicians": "3.9", "Parliament": "4.5", "Political Parties": "3.9", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "5.3"}, {"Country": "Belgi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "5.1", "Justice system": "4.9", "Police": "6.1", "Politicians": "4.3", "Parliament": "5.0", "Political Parties": "4.2", "European Parliament": "5.1", "UN": "5.5"}, {"Country": "Belgi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "5.0", "Justice system": "5.0", "Police": "6.0", "Politicians": "4.1", "Parliament": "4.8", "Political Parties": "4.1", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "5.2"}, {"Country": "Bulgarije", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Bulgarije", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Bulgarije", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Bulgarije", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "3.5", "Justice system": "2.3", "Police": "3.3", "Politicians": "1.6", "Parliament": "1.9", "Political Parties": "1.7", "European Parliament": "4.6", "UN": "4.8"}, {"Country": "Bulgarije", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "3.5", "Justice system": "2.5", "Police": "3.9", "Politicians": "2.0", "Parliament": "2.4", "Political Parties": "2.0", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "4.9"}, {"Country": "Bulgarije", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "3.4", "Justice system": "2.3", "Police": "3.6", "Politicians": "1.8", "Parliament": "2.1", "Political Parties": "1.8", "European Parliament": "4.3", "UN": "4.6"}, {"Country": "Bulgarije", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Cyprus", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Cyprus", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Cyprus", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Cyprus", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "4.5", "Justice system": "6.4", "Police": "5.9", "Politicians": "4.5", "Parliament": "5.6", "Political Parties": "4.4", "European Parliament": "6.0", "UN": "4.8"}, {"Country": "Cyprus", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "3.8", "Justice system": "5.6", "Police": "5.5", "Politicians": "3.6", "Parliament": "4.6", "Political Parties": "3.5", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "4.4"}, {"Country": "Cyprus", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "3.6", "Justice system": "4.7", "Police": "4.9", "Politicians": "2.5", "Parliament": "3.4", "Political Parties": "2.4", "European Parliament": "4.3", "UN": "3.7"}, {"Country": "Cyprus", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Denemarken", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "7.0", "Justice system": "7.1", "Police": "7.9", "Politicians": "5.5", "Parliament": "6.2", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "6.5"}, {"Country": "Denemarken", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "6.8", "Justice system": "7.2", "Police": "7.9", "Politicians": "5.6", "Parliament": "6.3", "Political Parties": "5.6", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "6.6"}, {"Country": "Denemarken", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "7.0", "Justice system": "7.5", "Police": "7.8", "Politicians": "5.6", "Parliament": "6.4", "Political Parties": "4.8", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "5.4"}, {"Country": "Denemarken", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "6.9", "Justice system": "7.3", "Police": "7.6", "Politicians": "5.6", "Parliament": "6.5", "Political Parties": "5.7", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "6.5"}, {"Country": "Denemarken", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "6.8", "Justice system": "7.4", "Police": "7.7", "Politicians": "5.0", "Parliament": "5.8", "Political Parties": "5.2", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "6.2"}, {"Country": "Denemarken", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "7.0", "Justice system": "7.7", "Police": "8.0", "Politicians": "5.2", "Parliament": "6.1", "Political Parties": "5.3", "European Parliament": "5.2", "UN": "6.6"}, {"Country": "Denemarken", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "6.9", "Justice system": "7.4", "Police": "7.7", "Politicians": "4.9", "Parliament": "5.9", "Political Parties": "5.1", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "6.3"}, {"Country": "Duitsland", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "4.7", "Justice system": "5.7", "Police": "6.7", "Politicians": "3.5", "Parliament": "4.5", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.5", "UN": "5.2"}, {"Country": "Duitsland", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "4.8", "Justice system": "5.5", "Police": "6.5", "Politicians": "3.2", "Parliament": "4.2", "Political Parties": "3.2", "European Parliament": "4.2", "UN": "4.9"}, {"Country": "Duitsland", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "4.8", "Justice system": "5.6", "Police": "6.6", "Politicians": "3.3", "Parliament": "4.2", "Political Parties": "3.3", "European Parliament": "4.1", "UN": "4.7"}, {"Country": "Duitsland", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "4.9", "Justice system": "5.8", "Police": "6.8", "Politicians": "3.5", "Parliament": "4.7", "Political Parties": "3.5", "European Parliament": "4.3", "UN": "5.0"}, {"Country": "Duitsland", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "4.7", "Justice system": "5.7", "Police": "6.9", "Politicians": "3.4", "Parliament": "4.3", "Political Parties": "3.4", "European Parliament": "4.0", "UN": "4.7"}, {"Country": "Duitsland", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "5.0", "Justice system": "6.0", "Police": "6.9", "Politicians": "3.8", "Parliament": "4.9", "Political Parties": "3.8", "European Parliament": "4.4", "UN": "5.1"}, {"Country": "Duitsland", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "5.1", "Justice system": "5.2", "Police": "6.7", "Politicians": "3.1", "Parliament": "3.6", "Political Parties": "2.9", "European Parliament": "4.4", "UN": "5.5"}, {"Country": "Estland", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Estland", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "5.2", "Justice system": "4.9", "Police": "5.7", "Politicians": "3.3", "Parliament": "4.2", "Political Parties": "3.1", "European Parliament": "4.9", "UN": "5.5"}, {"Country": "Estland", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "5.3", "Justice system": "5.1", "Police": "5.5", "Politicians": "3.5", "Parliament": "4.6", "Political Parties": "5.7", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "6.5"}, {"Country": "Estland", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "3.5", "Justice system": "2.3", "Police": "3.3", "Politicians": "1.6", "Parliament": "1.9", "Political Parties": "1.7", "European Parliament": "4.6", "UN": "4.8"}, {"Country": "Estland", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "5.7", "Justice system": "5.2", "Police": "6.2", "Politicians": "3.6", "Parliament": "4.2", "Political Parties": "3.4", "European Parliament": "5.2", "UN": "5.5"}, {"Country": "Estland", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "5.5", "Justice system": "4.9", "Police": "5.9", "Politicians": "3.3", "Parliament": "3.9", "Political Parties": "3.2", "European Parliament": "4.7", "UN": "5.2"}, {"Country": "Estland", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "5.6", "Justice system": "5.2", "Police": "6.1", "Politicians": "3.5", "Parliament": "4.4", "Political Parties": "3.4", "European Parliament": "4.4", "UN": "4.7"}, {"Country": "Finland", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "6.5", "Justice system": "6.8", "Police": "8.0", "Politicians": "4.8", "Parliament": "5.8", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.9", "UN": "6.5"}, {"Country": "Finland", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "6.5", "Justice system": "6.9", "Police": "8.0", "Politicians": "4.9", "Parliament": "6.0", "Political Parties": "5.0", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "6.6"}, {"Country": "Finland", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "6.6", "Justice system": "7.0", "Police": "8.0", "Politicians": "4.9", "Parliament": "6.0", "Political Parties": "3.5", "European Parliament": "5.3", "UN": "5.6"}, {"Country": "Finland", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "6.4", "Justice system": "7.1", "Police": "8.0", "Politicians": "4.9", "Parliament": "6.0", "Political Parties": "5.0", "European Parliament": "5.2", "UN": "6.7"}, {"Country": "Finland", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "6.5", "Justice system": "6.9", "Police": "8.0", "Politicians": "4.4", "Parliament": "5.4", "Political Parties": "4.5", "European Parliament": "5.1", "UN": "6.6"}, {"Country": "Finland", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "6.6", "Justice system": "7.0", "Police": "8.1", "Politicians": "4.8", "Parliament": "5.9", "Political Parties": "4.9", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "6.5"}, {"Country": "Finland", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "6.7", "Justice system": "6.8", "Police": "7.9", "Politicians": "4.6", "Parliament": "5.6", "Political Parties": "4.7", "European Parliament": "4.7", "UN": "6.2"}, {"Country": "Frankrijk", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "4.5", "Justice system": "4.8", "Police": "5.9", "Politicians": "3.7", "Parliament": "4.5", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.4", "UN": "4.6"}, {"Country": "Frankrijk", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "4.5", "Justice system": "4.8", "Police": "5.8", "Politicians": "3.5", "Parliament": "4.3", "Political Parties": "3.4", "European Parliament": "4.3", "UN": "4.7"}, {"Country": "Frankrijk", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "4.5", "Justice system": "4.9", "Police": "5.7", "Politicians": "3.3", "Parliament": "4.3", "Political Parties": "3.5", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "5.1"}, {"Country": "Frankrijk", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "4.5", "Justice system": "5.1", "Police": "5.8", "Politicians": "3.5", "Parliament": "4.5", "Political Parties": "3.4", "European Parliament": "4.6", "UN": "5.3"}, {"Country": "Frankrijk", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "4.3", "Justice system": "4.9", "Police": "5.6", "Politicians": "3.2", "Parliament": "4.1", "Political Parties": "3.1", "European Parliament": "4.3", "UN": "5.0"}, {"Country": "Frankrijk", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "4.4", "Justice system": "5.0", "Police": "5.9", "Politicians": "3.2", "Parliament": "4.1", "Political Parties": "3.1", "European Parliament": "4.1", "UN": "5.2"}, {"Country": "Frankrijk", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Griekenland", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Griekenland", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Griekenland", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Griekenland", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Griekenland", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "4.0", "Justice system": "3.8", "Police": "4.6", "Politicians": "1.4", "Parliament": "2.0", "Political Parties": "1.4", "European Parliament": "2.6", "UN": "2.6"}, {"Country": "Griekenland", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Griekenland", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Hongarije", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "4.1", "Justice system": "5.1", "Police": "4.9", "Politicians": "3.9", "Parliament": "5.0", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "5.7", "UN": "6.0"}, {"Country": "Hongarije", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "4.1", "Justice system": "4.4", "Police": "5.2", "Politicians": "2.7", "Parliament": "3.6", "Political Parties": "2.7", "European Parliament": "5.2", "UN": "5.7"}, {"Country": "Hongarije", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "4.3", "Justice system": "4.3", "Police": "5.1", "Politicians": "2.5", "Parliament": "3.4", "Political Parties": "5.0", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "6.5"}, {"Country": "Hongarije", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "4.1", "Justice system": "3.7", "Police": "4.3", "Politicians": "1.9", "Parliament": "2.6", "Political Parties": "2.0", "European Parliament": "4.0", "UN": "4.5"}, {"Country": "Hongarije", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "4.5", "Justice system": "4.6", "Police": "5.1", "Politicians": "3.1", "Parliament": "4.2", "Political Parties": "3.1", "European Parliament": "4.7", "UN": "5.1"}, {"Country": "Hongarije", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "4.8", "Justice system": "4.7", "Police": "5.3", "Politicians": "3.3", "Parliament": "3.9", "Political Parties": "3.2", "European Parliament": "4.2", "UN": "4.9"}, {"Country": "Hongarije", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "4.2", "Justice system": "4.6", "Police": "5.3", "Politicians": "2.9", "Parliament": "3.8", "Political Parties": "3.0", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "5.4"}, {"Country": "Ierland", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "5.5", "Justice system": "5.1", "Police": "6.5", "Politicians": "3.7", "Parliament": "4.4", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "5.1", "UN": "5.7"}, {"Country": "Ierland", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "5.8", "Justice system": "5.2", "Police": "6.6", "Politicians": "3.9", "Parliament": "4.7", "Political Parties": "4.0", "European Parliament": "5.4", "UN": "5.8"}, {"Country": "Ierland", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "5.4", "Justice system": "5.0", "Police": "6.1", "Politicians": "3.8", "Parliament": "4.8", "Political Parties": "3.2", "European Parliament": "4.4", "UN": "5.1"}, {"Country": "Ierland", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Ierland", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "5.3", "Justice system": "5.1", "Police": "6.5", "Politicians": "3.1", "Parliament": "3.7", "Political Parties": "3.1", "European Parliament": "4.1", "UN": "5.3"}, {"Country": "Ierland", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "5.2", "Justice system": "5.2", "Police": "6.6", "Politicians": "3.1", "Parliament": "3.6", "Political Parties": "3.0", "European Parliament": "4.4", "UN": "5.5"}, {"Country": "Ierland", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "5.2", "Justice system": "5.3", "Police": "6.3", "Politicians": "3.3", "Parliament": "3.8", "Political Parties": "3.3", "European Parliament": "4.6", "UN": "5.4"}, {"Country": "IJsland", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "IJsland", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "IJsland", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "IJsland", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "IJsland", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "IJsland", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "6.0", "Justice system": "5.8", "Police": "7.8", "Politicians": "3.9", "Parliament": "4.2", "Political Parties": "3.5", "European Parliament": "4.2", "UN": "6.3"}, {"Country": "IJsland", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Itali\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": " ", "Justice system": " ", "Police": " ", "Politicians": " ", "Parliament": " ", "Political Parties": " ", "European Parliament": " ", "UN": " "}, {"Country": "Itali\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": " ", "Justice system": " ", "Police": " ", "Politicians": " ", "Parliament": " ", "Political Parties": " ", "European Parliament": " ", "UN": " "}, {"Country": "Itali\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": " ", "Justice system": " ", "Police": " ", "Politicians": " ", "Parliament": " ", "Political Parties": " ", "European Parliament": " ", "UN": " "}, {"Country": "Itali\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": " ", "Justice system": " ", "Police": " ", "Politicians": " ", "Parliament": " ", "Political Parties": " ", "European Parliament": " ", "UN": " "}, {"Country": "Itali\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": " ", "Justice system": " ", "Police": " ", "Politicians": " ", "Parliament": " ", "Political Parties": " ", "European Parliament": " ", "UN": " "}, {"Country": "Itali\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "4.8", "Justice system": "4.5", "Police": "6.1", "Politicians": "2.0", "Parliament": "3.2", "Political Parties": "2.0", "European Parliament": "4.3", "UN": "5.2"}, {"Country": "Itali\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Kosovo", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Kosovo", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Kosovo", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Kosovo", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Kosovo", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Kosovo", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "3.7", "Justice system": "3.2", "Police": "5.6", "Politicians": "2.1", "Parliament": "3.1", "Political Parties": "2.3", "European Parliament": "5.3", "UN": "6.1"}, {"Country": "Kosovo", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Kroati\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Kroati\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Kroati\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Kroati\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Kroati\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "4.6", "Justice system": "3.2", "Police": "4.4", "Politicians": "1.6", "Parliament": "2.3", "Political Parties": "1.8", "European Parliament": "3.3", "UN": "3.9"}, {"Country": "Kroati\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Kroati\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Litouwen", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": " ", "Justice system": " ", "Police": " ", "Politicians": " ", "Parliament": " ", "Political Parties": " ", "European Parliament": " ", "UN": " "}, {"Country": "Litouwen", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": " ", "Justice system": " ", "Police": " ", "Politicians": " ", "Parliament": " ", "Political Parties": " ", "European Parliament": " ", "UN": " "}, {"Country": "Litouwen", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": " ", "Justice system": " ", "Police": " ", "Politicians": " ", "Parliament": " ", "Political Parties": " ", "European Parliament": " ", "UN": " "}, {"Country": "Litouwen", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": " ", "Justice system": " ", "Police": " ", "Politicians": " ", "Parliament": " ", "Political Parties": " ", "European Parliament": " ", "UN": " "}, {"Country": "Litouwen", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": " ", "Justice system": " ", "Police": " ", "Politicians": " ", "Parliament": " ", "Political Parties": " ", "European Parliament": " ", "UN": " "}, {"Country": "Litouwen", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "5.2", "Justice system": "4.0", "Police": "5.5", "Politicians": "2.9", "Parliament": "3.1", "Political Parties": "2.8", "European Parliament": "4.7", "UN": "5.0"}, {"Country": "Litouwen", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "4.9", "Justice system": "4.5", "Police": "5.7", "Politicians": "3.1", "Parliament": "3.3", "Political Parties": "3.0", "European Parliament": "5.2", "UN": "5.6"}, {"Country": "Nederland", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "5.7", "Justice system": "5.4", "Police": "5.8", "Politicians": "4.9", "Parliament": "5.2", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.7", "UN": "5.4"}, {"Country": "Nederland", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "5.8", "Justice system": "5.5", "Police": "6.0", "Politicians": "4.7", "Parliament": "4.7", "Political Parties": "4.8", "European Parliament": "4.6", "UN": "5.4"}, {"Country": "Nederland", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "5.8", "Justice system": "5.8", "Police": "6.2", "Politicians": "5.0", "Parliament": "5.3", "Political Parties": "3.5", "European Parliament": "3.5", "UN": "5.0"}, {"Country": "Nederland", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "6.0", "Justice system": "5.9", "Police": "6.3", "Politicians": "5.2", "Parliament": "5.6", "Political Parties": "5.2", "European Parliament": "5.1", "UN": "5.6"}, {"Country": "Nederland", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "6.0", "Justice system": "5.9", "Police": "6.3", "Politicians": "5.2", "Parliament": "5.4", "Political Parties": "5.3", "European Parliament": "4.9", "UN": "5.6"}, {"Country": "Nederland", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "6.0", "Justice system": "6.1", "Police": "6.4", "Politicians": "5.1", "Parliament": "5.3", "Political Parties": "5.1", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "5.7"}, {"Country": "Nederland", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "6.0", "Justice system": "6.0", "Police": "6.4", "Politicians": "4.9", "Parliament": "5.2", "Political Parties": "4.9", "European Parliament": "4.5", "UN": "5.5"}, {"Country": "Noorwegen", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "6.6", "Justice system": "6.3", "Police": "7.0", "Politicians": "4.6", "Parliament": "5.7", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.7", "UN": "6.8"}, {"Country": "Noorwegen", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "6.6", "Justice system": "6.4", "Police": "7.1", "Politicians": "4.2", "Parliament": "5.4", "Political Parties": "4.3", "European Parliament": "4.6", "UN": "6.9"}, {"Country": "Noorwegen", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "6.8", "Justice system": "6.6", "Police": "7.2", "Politicians": "4.4", "Parliament": "5.7", "Political Parties": "2.6", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "5.4"}, {"Country": "Noorwegen", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "6.6", "Justice system": "6.8", "Police": "7.0", "Politicians": "4.6", "Parliament": "5.8", "Political Parties": "4.8", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "6.8"}, {"Country": "Noorwegen", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "6.7", "Justice system": "6.9", "Police": "7.2", "Politicians": "4.9", "Parliament": "6.0", "Political Parties": "4.9", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "6.7"}, {"Country": "Noorwegen", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "6.7", "Justice system": "7.2", "Police": "7.2", "Politicians": "5.1", "Parliament": "6.3", "Political Parties": "5.2", "European Parliament": "4.9", "UN": "6.7"}, {"Country": "Noorwegen", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "6.6", "Justice system": "7.2", "Police": "7.4", "Politicians": "5.3", "Parliament": "6.7", "Political Parties": "5.3", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "6.7"}, {"Country": "Oekra\u00c3\u00afne", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Oekra\u00c3\u00afne", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Oekra\u00c3\u00afne", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Oekra\u00c3\u00afne", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Oekra\u00c3\u00afne", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "4.2", "Justice system": "2.3", "Police": "2.5", "Politicians": "1.8", "Parliament": "2.0", "Political Parties": "2.0", "European Parliament": "4.0", "UN": "4.0"}, {"Country": "Oekra\u00c3\u00afne", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "4.5", "Justice system": "1.9", "Police": "2.0", "Politicians": "1.7", "Parliament": "1.8", "Political Parties": "1.9", "European Parliament": "3.9", "UN": "3.9"}, {"Country": "Oekra\u00c3\u00afne", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Oostenrijk", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "5.1", "Justice system": "6.1", "Police": "6.4", "Politicians": "3.5", "Parliament": "5.1", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.2", "UN": "4.5"}, {"Country": "Oostenrijk", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "5.2", "Justice system": "5.8", "Police": "6.2", "Politicians": "3.3", "Parliament": "4.8", "Political Parties": "3.4", "European Parliament": "4.0", "UN": "4.5"}, {"Country": "Oostenrijk", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "5.1", "Justice system": "6.0", "Police": "6.3", "Politicians": "3.3", "Parliament": "4.9", "Political Parties": "3.3", "European Parliament": "4.0", "UN": "4.7"}, {"Country": "Oostenrijk", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Oostenrijk", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Oostenrijk", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Oostenrijk", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "5.0", "Justice system": "5.7", "Police": "6.5", "Politicians": "3.5", "Parliament": "4.7", "Political Parties": "3.4", "European Parliament": "3.6", "UN": "4.4"}, {"Country": "Polen", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "3.7", "Justice system": "3.7", "Police": "4.9", "Politicians": "2.7", "Parliament": "3.5", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "5.6"}, {"Country": "Polen", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "3.6", "Justice system": "3.0", "Police": "4.6", "Politicians": "1.9", "Parliament": "2.4", "Political Parties": "1.9", "European Parliament": "4.3", "UN": "5.0"}, {"Country": "Polen", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "4.1", "Justice system": "3.8", "Police": "5.0", "Politicians": "2.1", "Parliament": "2.7", "Political Parties": "3.9", "European Parliament": "5.3", "UN": "5.7"}, {"Country": "Polen", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "4.1", "Justice system": "3.9", "Police": "5.1", "Politicians": "2.3", "Parliament": "3.0", "Political Parties": "2.3", "European Parliament": "4.5", "UN": "5.1"}, {"Country": "Polen", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "4.4", "Justice system": "4.3", "Police": "5.4", "Politicians": "2.7", "Parliament": "3.4", "Political Parties": "2.5", "European Parliament": "4.7", "UN": "5.3"}, {"Country": "Polen", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "4.1", "Justice system": "3.7", "Police": "5.3", "Politicians": "2.2", "Parliament": "3.0", "Political Parties": "2.2", "European Parliament": "4.2", "UN": "5.0"}, {"Country": "Polen", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "3.9", "Justice system": "3.5", "Police": "5.1", "Politicians": "2.0", "Parliament": "2.8", "Political Parties": "2.0", "European Parliament": "3.6", "UN": "4.6"}, {"Country": "Portugal", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "4.2", "Justice system": "4.3", "Police": "5.1", "Politicians": "2.8", "Parliament": "4.4", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "5.4"}, {"Country": "Portugal", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "3.9", "Justice system": "3.9", "Police": "5.1", "Politicians": "2.1", "Parliament": "3.7", "Political Parties": "2.1", "European Parliament": "4.0", "UN": "4.7"}, {"Country": "Portugal", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "4.1", "Justice system": "4.0", "Police": "5.1", "Politicians": "2.5", "Parliament": "3.8", "Political Parties": "5.1", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "5.5"}, {"Country": "Portugal", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "3.7", "Justice system": "3.8", "Police": "5.3", "Politicians": "2.3", "Parliament": "3.5", "Political Parties": "2.4", "European Parliament": "4.3", "UN": "4.9"}, {"Country": "Portugal", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "3.7", "Justice system": "3.5", "Police": "5.1", "Politicians": "2.0", "Parliament": "2.9", "Political Parties": "2.0", "European Parliament": "3.7", "UN": "4.3"}, {"Country": "Portugal", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "3.6", "Justice system": "3.5", "Police": "5.3", "Politicians": "1.8", "Parliament": "2.5", "Political Parties": "1.8", "European Parliament": "3.2", "UN": "4.1"}, {"Country": "Portugal", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "3.6", "Justice system": "3.7", "Police": "5.6", "Politicians": "2.0", "Parliament": "3.1", "Political Parties": "2.2", "European Parliament": "3.4", "UN": "4.6"}, {"Country": "Sloveni\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "4.0", "Justice system": "4.3", "Police": "4.9", "Politicians": "3.1", "Parliament": "4.0", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.6", "UN": "4.9"}, {"Country": "Sloveni\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "6.1", "Justice system": "5.8", "Police": "6.5", "Politicians": "4.2", "Parliament": "5.4", "Political Parties": "4.4", "European Parliament": "4.0", "UN": "6.3"}, {"Country": "Sloveni\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "4.1", "Justice system": "4.2", "Police": "5.0", "Politicians": "3.2", "Parliament": "4.2", "Political Parties": "4.5", "European Parliament": "4.7", "UN": "6.8"}, {"Country": "Sloveni\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "4.3", "Justice system": "4.3", "Police": "5.0", "Politicians": "3.4", "Parliament": "4.4", "Political Parties": "3.4", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "5.0"}, {"Country": "Sloveni\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "3.9", "Justice system": "3.1", "Police": "5.0", "Politicians": "2.3", "Parliament": "3.0", "Political Parties": "2.2", "European Parliament": "3.7", "UN": "4.1"}, {"Country": "Sloveni\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "4.6", "Justice system": "3.3", "Police": "5.3", "Politicians": "2.3", "Parliament": "3.0", "Political Parties": "2.3", "European Parliament": "3.8", "UN": "4.2"}, {"Country": "Sloveni\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "4.1", "Justice system": "3.1", "Police": "5.5", "Politicians": "1.9", "Parliament": "2.8", "Political Parties": "2.0", "European Parliament": "3.4", "UN": "4.2"}, {"Country": "Slowakije", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Slowakije", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "4.1", "Justice system": "3.8", "Police": "4.7", "Politicians": "3.1", "Parliament": "4.1", "Political Parties": "3.2", "European Parliament": "4.5", "UN": "4.6"}, {"Country": "Slowakije", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "4.3", "Justice system": "4.2", "Police": "4.7", "Politicians": "3.6", "Parliament": "4.2", "Political Parties": "2.1", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "5.3"}, {"Country": "Slowakije", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "4.1", "Justice system": "4.1", "Police": "4.8", "Politicians": "3.6", "Parliament": "4.0", "Political Parties": "3.6", "European Parliament": "5.2", "UN": "5.4"}, {"Country": "Slowakije", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "4.5", "Justice system": "3.5", "Police": "4.5", "Politicians": "2.8", "Parliament": "3.2", "Political Parties": "2.7", "European Parliament": "4.4", "UN": "4.8"}, {"Country": "Slowakije", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "3.8", "Justice system": "3.2", "Police": "4.1", "Politicians": "2.8", "Parliament": "3.1", "Political Parties": "2.7", "European Parliament": "3.7", "UN": "4.2"}, {"Country": "Slowakije", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Spanje", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "4.9", "Justice system": "4.3", "Police": "5.4", "Politicians": "3.4", "Parliament": "4.8", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "4.7"}, {"Country": "Spanje", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "4.9", "Justice system": "4.7", "Police": "5.9", "Politicians": "3.7", "Parliament": "5.1", "Political Parties": "3.7", "European Parliament": "5.1", "UN": "5.0"}, {"Country": "Spanje", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "5.1", "Justice system": "5.0", "Police": "6.0", "Politicians": "3.5", "Parliament": "5.0", "Political Parties": "2.5", "European Parliament": "4.6", "UN": "4.9"}, {"Country": "Spanje", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "4.9", "Justice system": "4.3", "Police": "6.1", "Politicians": "3.3", "Parliament": "5.0", "Political Parties": "3.2", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "5.0"}, {"Country": "Spanje", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "5.1", "Justice system": "4.4", "Police": "6.3", "Politicians": "2.7", "Parliament": "4.3", "Political Parties": "2.7", "European Parliament": "4.5", "UN": "5.0"}, {"Country": "Spanje", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "5.1", "Justice system": "3.7", "Police": "5.9", "Politicians": "1.9", "Parliament": "3.4", "Political Parties": "1.9", "European Parliament": "3.9", "UN": "4.7"}, {"Country": "Spanje", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "4.8", "Justice system": "4.0", "Police": "6.3", "Politicians": "2.2", "Parliament": "3.7", "Political Parties": "2.2", "European Parliament": "3.8", "UN": "4.8"}, {"Country": "Tsjechi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Tsjechi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Tsjechi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Tsjechi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": ".", "Justice system": ".", "Police": ".", "Politicians": ".", "Parliament": ".", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": ".", "UN": "."}, {"Country": "Tsjechi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "4.6", "Justice system": "4.1", "Police": "4.9", "Politicians": "2.6", "Parliament": "3.3", "Political Parties": "2.7", "European Parliament": "4.1", "UN": "4.9"}, {"Country": "Tsjechi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "4.5", "Justice system": "4.1", "Police": "5.1", "Politicians": "2.6", "Parliament": "3.2", "Political Parties": "2.7", "European Parliament": "3.9", "UN": "4.8"}, {"Country": "Tsjechi\u00c3\u00ab", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "4.6", "Justice system": "4.7", "Police": "5.7", "Politicians": "3.3", "Parliament": "4.0", "Political Parties": "3.4", "European Parliament": "4.2", "UN": "4.8"}, {"Country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "5.1", "Justice system": "5.0", "Police": "6.0", "Politicians": "3.8", "Parliament": "4.7", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "3.6", "UN": "5.3"}, {"Country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "5.2", "Justice system": "5.1", "Police": "6.1", "Politicians": "3.6", "Parliament": "4.3", "Political Parties": "3.7", "European Parliament": "3.5", "UN": "5.2"}, {"Country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "5.4", "Justice system": "5.0", "Police": "6.0", "Politicians": "3.4", "Parliament": "4.2", "Political Parties": "4.6", "European Parliament": "4.5", "UN": "6.4"}, {"Country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "5.3", "Justice system": "5.2", "Police": "6.2", "Politicians": "3.6", "Parliament": "4.3", "Political Parties": "3.6", "European Parliament": "3.6", "UN": "5.1"}, {"Country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "5.4", "Justice system": "5.2", "Police": "6.2", "Politicians": "3.4", "Parliament": "4.1", "Political Parties": "3.5", "European Parliament": "3.4", "UN": "4.9"}, {"Country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "5.4", "Justice system": "5.6", "Police": "6.6", "Politicians": "3.7", "Parliament": "4.3", "Political Parties": "3.7", "European Parliament": "3.4", "UN": "5.2"}, {"Country": "Verenigd Koninkrijk", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "5.4", "Justice system": "5.6", "Police": "6.3", "Politicians": "3.5", "Parliament": "4.3", "Political Parties": "3.5", "European Parliament": "3.1", "UN": "4.9"}, {"Country": "Zweden", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "6.1", "Justice system": "6.1", "Police": "6.8", "Politicians": "4.7", "Parliament": "5.9", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.0", "UN": "6.6"}, {"Country": "Zweden", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "6.1", "Justice system": "5.8", "Police": "6.5", "Politicians": "4.2", "Parliament": "5.4", "Political Parties": "4.4", "European Parliament": "4.0", "UN": "6.3"}, {"Country": "Zweden", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "6.3", "Justice system": "6.0", "Police": "6.5", "Politicians": "4.5", "Parliament": "5.6", "Political Parties": "3.2", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "5.1"}, {"Country": "Zweden", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "6.4", "Justice system": "6.1", "Police": "6.6", "Politicians": "4.6", "Parliament": "5.7", "Political Parties": "4.8", "European Parliament": "4.7", "UN": "6.4"}, {"Country": "Zweden", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "6.3", "Justice system": "6.5", "Police": "7.0", "Politicians": "5.0", "Parliament": "6.3", "Political Parties": "5.1", "European Parliament": "5.0", "UN": "6.3"}, {"Country": "Zweden", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "6.0", "Justice system": "6.3", "Police": "6.7", "Politicians": "4.7", "Parliament": "5.9", "Political Parties": "4.9", "European Parliament": "4.7", "UN": "6.3"}, {"Country": "Zweden", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "6.2", "Justice system": "6.4", "Police": "6.9", "Politicians": "5.0", "Parliament": "6.2", "Political Parties": "5.1", "European Parliament": "4.7", "UN": "6.4"}, {"Country": "Zwitserland", "Year": "2002", "Humanity": "5.6", "Justice system": "6.2", "Police": "6.8", "Politicians": "4.9", "Parliament": "5.8", "Political Parties": ".", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "5.4"}, {"Country": "Zwitserland", "Year": "2004", "Humanity": "5.7", "Justice system": "6.1", "Police": "6.9", "Politicians": "4.8", "Parliament": "5.5", "Political Parties": "4.6", "European Parliament": "4.6", "UN": "5.4"}, {"Country": "Zwitserland", "Year": "2006", "Humanity": "5.7", "Justice system": "6.2", "Police": "6.9", "Politicians": "4.9", "Parliament": "5.8", "Political Parties": "3.6", "European Parliament": "5.1", "UN": "5.3"}, {"Country": "Zwitserland", "Year": "2008", "Humanity": "5.7", "Justice system": "6.4", "Police": "6.9", "Politicians": "4.9", "Parliament": "5.8", "Political Parties": "4.7", "European Parliament": "4.8", "UN": "5.6"}, {"Country": "Zwitserland", "Year": "2010", "Humanity": "5.6", "Justice system": "6.3", "Police": "7.0", "Politicians": "5.0", "Parliament": "5.8", "Political Parties": "4.8", "European Parliament": "4.6", "UN": "5.3"}, {"Country": "Zwitserland", "Year": "2012", "Humanity": "5.7", "Justice system": "6.5", "Police": "7.2", "Politicians": "5.2", "Parliament": "6.1", "Political Parties": "5.0", "European Parliament": "4.7", "UN": "5.5"}, {"Country": "Zwitserland", "Year": "2014*", "Humanity": "5.7", "Justice system": "6.6", "Police": "7.2", "Politicians": "5.2", "Parliament": "6.2", "Political Parties": "5.1", "European Parliament": "4.5", "UN": "5.4"}]}